NARRAToR:
Previously on Two and a Half Men:
You were meant for each other.
What could come between you?
- My sister.
- You got a sister?
You know what, Herb? Judith can relax.
I'm gonna check into a hotel.
Myra, no, you don't have to do that.
Yes, she does.
Hey, wait.
You don't have to stay at a hotel.
- I got plenty of room at my place.
- Yeah, I'll bet you do.
No strings attached.
Why can't I sleep in my bed?
Aunt Myra's not there.
I'm sure she will be. She's probably
just getting something in the kitchen.
That's not the kitchen.
Thinking of chewing your arm off?
What? No, no, no. Why would I do that?
I don't know, maybe because
you're not horny anymore...
...and you just remembered
I'm staying through the weekend.
Wow, you got all that from the twitching
of my shoulder muscles?
I have those muscles too, Charlie.
Okay, good to know.
Well, to be honest,
I did have a momentary panic reflex...
...but it passed,
and I'm actually happy you're here.
You sound surprised.
Surprised doesn't begin to cover it.
Normally at this point in a relationship, I'm
busy plotting the appropriate exit strategy.
For example?
Well...
...that would depend on whether I'm trying
to get rid of you just for today or forever.
Let's say today.
Okay, today I have to see my dermatologist
about a little rash.
Oh, that's good.
All right, what about forever?
Turns out it wasrt a rash
and they won't let me come home.
- Impressive.
- Thank you.
I'm kind of a savant.
Looks like you're good at two things.
What's the other one?
- Oh, right.
- The piano.
Okay, I just checked.
No one slept in my bed all night.
None of your business who slept where.
Excuse me, but if who sleeps in my bed
is not my business, then what is?
Let it go, Goldilocks.
- Morning.
And how many times do you have to get up
to go pee?
- I wasrt counting.
- I was. Four.
- One was to get a glass of water.
- There's your problem.
Stop topping off the tank.
- What's going on?
- I had to sleep in Dad's room last night.
Uncle Charlie invited Aunt Myra to stay
in my room but it turns out...
Got it.
Well, do you think it's fair?
Nothing about your uncle Charlie's life
is fair.
Finish your breakfast.
We'll get you fitted for a tux.
- Why do I have to wear a tuxedo?
- Your mother's getting married.
- You're in the wedding party.
- Why do I have to be in the party?
Your mother still thinks you're cute.
- Morning.
Morning.
Everybody get a good sleep?
- No.
So, Charlie, where's this house guest
I'm hearing about?
Uh, gee, I guess she's probably
still asleep in Jake's room.
Oh, please. You are such a liar.
- What?
- Forget it, Charlie. We know.
- You do?
We do.
Okay, well, I got a good night's sleep.
Probably because Aunt Myra
doesn't pee a lot.
- Can I talk with you in private?
- Oh, come on. It's no big deal.
I was in the middle of flossing
and suddenly there she is...
...sitting on my bed...
- Ah-ah-ah!
He doesn't need to hear this.
Fine.
Like I didn't hear enough last night.
Okay. Uh...
Let me just start by saying I applaud
the gusto with which you approach life.
Thank you.
That being said...
...are you out of your freaking mind?
- Beg pardon?
- You just could not control yourself.
A female's in the house,
she must be mounted.
No, it's not like that at all.
And why do you even care?
Why? You ask me why?
Never mind. Not important.
I will tell you why.
Because every time you rut
with any woman...
...even remotely connected to my life,
I end up suffering.
- Oh, that's ridiculous.
- Ridiculous, you say?
All right, all right,
let's look at the record.
- You slept with Judith's sister...
- Well, yeah, but...
- at my wedding reception.
All right, poor timing.
You had more sex on my wedding day
than I did.
That part's not my fault.
Okay, okay, let's jump ahead.
When Judith was divorcing me...
...who seduced
and then abandoned my lawyer...
...causing her to take revenge on me?
- Now, hold on, that chick was nuts.
- I lost everything.
Well, to be fair, you didn't have
that much to begin with.
And now...
...that Judith
is finally getting remarried...
...and I can see the light at the end
of the alimony tunnel...
...you decide, "Hey, why don't
I start humping her new sister-in-law?"
- That is not how it happened.
- I don't care how it happened.
I only care how it's gonna end.
And it's gonna end badly for me.
How? Explain how.
I don't know yet.
That's always part of the fun.
Trying to guess how your penis
is gonna bite me in the ass.
Alan, you gotta believe me here.
This is different. I really like Myra.
Oh, you like all of them.
And then you don't.
What's gonna happen
when you get tired...
...of this poor gi...?
Morning.
- Morning.
Boy, I slept great.
- Jake's bed is really comfortable.
- Don't bother, he knows.
Oh. Boy, I slept great.
Charlie's a terrific lover.
Oh, this one's gonna be bad.
I don't understand
why I can't have the blue tuxedo.
You're going to your mother's wedding...
...not hosting a game show
on Telemundo.
This from a grown man
wearing a green polo shirt.
All the other men are gonna
be wearing black tuxedos.
If the other men were jumping off
a bridge, would you want me to?
If it'd keep your mother
off my back, yes.
- I'll get the jacket.
- Thank you.
Listen, this is a very big day
for your mother.
It's important that you cooperate
and make her proud of you.
I'm her son. She has to be proud of me.
You think so, huh?
Have you met my mother?
Oh, yeah.
Let me explain something to you.
A womars wedding day is something
she will remember for the rest of her life.
So if you screw it up, she will never forgive
you, even if it was your brother's fault...
...and there was nothing you could do
to prevent it short of having him fixed.
Don't worry, Dad. It'll be fine.
- Thank you.
- I don't have a brother.
Hey, listen, we haven't really talked
about what all this means.
- What "what" means?
- Well, the big changes that are happening.
It's just a couple of hairs, Dad.
It's not that big a deal.
Not those changes.
The wedding. You're gonna have
a stepdad in your life.
- So?
- So is there anything you wanna talk about?
Do you have any questions?
- Just one.
- Yeah, buddy?
Why can't I wear the blue tuxedo?
Jake, your dinner's getting cold.
So, what did you guys do today?
We went on the Universal Studios Tour...
...and then Charlie took me
to the Hollywood Wax Museum.
You're kidding?
I thought you hate that stuff.
What gave you that idea?
Whenever I ask if you
to go someplace like that, you say:
"I hate that touristy stuff. "
- Well, this is different.
- How?
I enjoy her company.
And it's my first trip to L.A.,
so I wanna do all the traditional stuff.
Tomorrow we're gonna sit in rush-hour
traffic and give other drivers the finger.
Good evening.
- Why are you wearing that?
- You said I look great.
I don't want you messing it up
before your mom's wedding.
I won't mess it up.
Alan, you gotta admit he lends
a bit of class to the place.
Thank you, my good man.
Hey, speaking of the wedding, Charlie,
I have a favor I'd like to ask.
- Sure.
- I have to be there and I was just thinking...
...that the only way it is gonna be any fun
is if you come with me.
You want me to be your date
at Judith's wedding?
Yeah.
We'll have some laughs.
What do you say?
I'm laughing already.
Uh-oh.
Well, that's too bad, Herb. You tell Judith
if she wants me to be a bridesmaid...
...and wear that brown satin
turd of a dress...
...then I am entitled to bring whoever I want
as a date and I want Charlie.
Okay, bye.
See? No problem.
Hi, Judith.
Problem.
Here's your suit.
Thanks, Berta.
The dry cleaners found $46
and a condom in the breast pocket.
Here's the condom.
Again, thanks.
Can I give you some free advice?
Free? I'm already down $46.
What is it you say about going to a wedding
with a woman you're sleeping with?
This is different.
You say, and I quote,
"Better I should light myself on fire...
...and run through a meth lab. "
Oh, well, that's just a figure of speech.
Come on, Charlie,
what are you doing with this girl?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, she's a nice kid.
You're gonna break her heart.
- You don't know that.
- I know you.
Myra's not one of your Handi Wipes
in high heels you can throw out...
...after you wipe your Handi.
You don't know
what you're talking about...
...because this relationship
is not based on sex.
Not based on sex?
Well, unless she sweats bourbon
and farts hundred-dollar bills...
...what exactly
is gonna keep you together?
Oh, crap.
No, you listen to me.
If Myra wants to bring Charlie
to the wedding, that's her business.
No, I will not intervene and you're just
gonna have to live with it. Goodbye.
- I changed my mind. I'm not going.
- Oh, thank God.
Judith, great news.
I talked him out of it.
- Hey.
- What you doing?
- Grading tests.
- Tenth-grade economics?
- Uh-huh.
- Ask me a question.
- Okay.
The functions and implications
of monetary policy are...
Never mind.
You sure? I grade on a curve.
That's all right.
I'm stupid on a straight line.
Listen...
...about the wedding.
I don't think I should go.
Okay.
I'm just concerned that maybe
we should slow things down a bit.
What things?
You know, things.
I mean...
...you don't know me that well...
...and I'm afraid that I might hurt you
without meaning to.
- Don't worry about it.
- Okay, good. I won't.
Exactly what is it
I'm not worrying about?
- Hurting me.
- Right.
Why am I not worrying about that?
I'm a big girl, Charlie.
Some might even say a woman.
I wanna go to the wedding with you.
Don't worry about Jake.
I'll get him there in time.
Well, you are very welcome.
Best of luck to you and Herb.
- Bye-bye.
- I'm going to the wedding.
What is this, candle wax?
How do you get candle wax on the seat
of your pants?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
Okay, I might have lit a couple farts.
- I'm ready. Myra's ready. Is he ready?
- Does he look ready?
Well, he's not wearing any pants.
That's ready for some things.
Just go ahead. I'll get him there.
Okay.
What is that?
Pudding.
You know what?
I just realized something.
I am two for two at Judith's weddings.
What a coincidence.
I'm two for two at Herb's weddings.
Huh.
Okay, what about funerals?
Can you beat a three-way in a hearse?
No.
You have to think about it?
It's a gray area.
Where have you been?
I was looking for you.
- We were having sex in the coatroom.
- Ha, ha. Good one.
One of my groomsmen
got food poisoning.
Walk down the aisle with Uncle Fred.
Uncle Fred? Is that the only man left?
Well, there's cousin Trudy.
She's pre-op,
but she's wearing a very nice tux.
Why can't I just walk down the aisle
with Charlie?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I'm just
an innocent bystander at this shindig.
Oh, picture the look on Judith's face
when she sees you at the altar.
I'm in.
Oh, God.
- Herb. Herb.
- Oh, hi.
Thanks for bringing him down.
Oh, you look very handsome, Jake.
I know. It's the tux.
Okay, well, congratulations.
I wish you both a lot of happiness.
- Thanks.
- Don't make the same mistakes I did.
I won't. She wrote them down for me.
Good.
- All right, buddy, have fun.
- Okay.
Oh, remember that tux is a rental.
Excuse me.
Are you Judith's ex-husband?
Yeah, I was just dropping off our son.
I'm sorry, do I know you?
Oh, no. Not really. It's...
Herb and I were engaged
before he met Judith, so...
- And you're coming to his wedding?
- Yeah, we're still friends.
Well, how very California of you.
Yeah. Well, I wish him the best.
I have to tell you,
based on first impressions...
...I'm not sure
that Judith is trading up.
Oh, thank you.
And having just met you...
...I feel safe in saying that Herb's
not getting an upgrade either.
Oh, man.
- Nice dress.
- Bite me.
Okay. Meet me in the coatroom.
Listen, after the reception,
can you take me to the airport?
- You're flying home tonight?
- Yeah.
- I thought we had something going here.
- We did. Now I'm going home.
Okay. Maybe I can come visit you
sometime.
I don't think my boyfriend
would like that very much.
You got a boyfriend?
- He's more like a fiancé.
- You're getting married?
Why didn't you tell me you were engaged?
I thought it'd be awkward.
Awkward?
You may be seated.
Mm. Oh. We really
shouldn't be doing this.
- Why not? They broke our hearts.
- Yeah, but I'm kind of over it.
I'm not.
Hang on. Hang on. Hang on.
Maybe we can go out for coffee first.
Or a movie.
Alan, this is gonna happen with you
or without you.
With me or...
How does that work?
The institution of marriage
is not one to enter lightly.
So we pause at this time to consider
the depth of that commitment.
SHANNoN:
Oh, Alan Harper, you animal.
I can't believe Judith let you go.
Oh, God, Alan Harper. Oh, God.
Oh, don't stop, Alan Harper.
Please don't stop.
Oh, Alan Harper.
I feel like a woman again.
I'm Alan Harper, and I'm not having sex.
- Hey.
How was the reception?
Kind of a letdown after the ceremony.
But you'll be happy to know your
little outburst is already on YouTube.
Damn camera phones.
- Boy, is Mom mad at you.
- Yeah.
She might start her second marriage
the same way as the first.
So, ahem...
...drinking in the dark, eh?
It wasrt dark when I started.
- Did you get Myra to the airport?
- Yep.
And you know what?
I'll never see her again.
I was just a meaningless fling
to that girl.
Huh. I'll bet this is that whole
karma thing people talk about.
Could be.
You know that feeling you get when...
...somebody's gone from your life...
...and you suddenly realize
that you miss them?
Yeah?
I don't care for it.
Hey, you know what always
cheers me up?
Pigs in a blanket.